Creates a new app version, uploads it along with your source for review, and then files a publish request for you app.

USAGE
  $ devvit publish [--config <value>] [--bump major|minor|patch |
    --version <value>] [--copy-paste] [-v] [--public | --withdraw]

FLAGS
  -v, --verbose      Enable verbose logging
  --bump=<option>    Type of version bump (major|minor|patch). Patch by default.
                     <options: major|minor|patch>
  --config=<value>   path to devvit config file
  --copy-paste       Copy-paste the auth code instead of opening a browser
  --public           Submit the app for review to be published publicly (as
                     opposed to unlisted, the default)
  --version=<value>  Explicit version number (e.g: 1.0.1). Note that prerelease
                     versions are not allowed to be published.
  --withdraw         Withdraw the most recent publish request for your app (if
                     it exists and is pending)

DESCRIPTION
  Creates a new app version, uploads it along with your source for review, and
  then files a publish request for you app.

